(Amy:)That's nice.
(Amy:)I'm fine.
(Amy:)Hey, listen,
I've been meaning to ask,
(Amy:)how come Aunt Doe and
Aunt Florence never got along?
(Penny:)Okay, just...
give me that.
(Penny:)Amy broke up with Sheldon,
(Penny:)she got her ears pierced
(Penny:)and she made us
eat penis cookies!
(Penny:)Hang on.
(Penny:)She wants to talk to you.
(Leonard:)I don't think
the lever's working.
WOLOWITZ:
What makes you say that?
(Leonard:)There's gotta be
something else we could try.
If this was Star Trek,
(Raj:)we could use a phaser
to blast it off.
(Howard:)No, it's too
broad of a beam.
(Howard:)You'd need something
more precise,
(Howard:)like Superman's heat vision.
(Sheldon:)Ooh, the Green
Lantern's ring
(Sheldon:)could make a big green
hand that unscrews it.
(Raj:)If you need
a green hand,
(Raj:)why not just
use the Hulk?
(Sheldon:)Oh, please, the Hulk
would never get
(Sheldon:)across the border
with that temper.
LEONARD:
Guys, excuse me,
(Leonard:)not that calling
one of the Avengers
(Leonard:)isn't a perfectly
reasonable choice,